<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Hisanth Photography</string>
    <string name="ad_id">ca-app-pub-2373003321681741~7281773351</string>
    <string name="google_maps_key">AIzaSyAO-yZ3wHsZjTCyX9f-WXxYQzdftUGD95s</string>

    <string name="name">Name *</string>
    <string name="gpsAddress">Auto Address Capture</string>
    <string name="address">Address *</string>
    <string name="locality">Locality *</string>
    <string name="city">City *</string>
    <string name="pincode">PinCode *</string>
    <string name="mobile">Mobile Number *</string>
    <string name="email">Email ID *</string>
    <string name="services">Required Service *</string>
    <string name="date">Date Of Function *</string>
    <string name="delivery_mode">Mode Of Delivery *</string>
    <string name="name_hint">Please Enter Your Name</string>
    <string name="address_hint">Please Enter Your Address</string>
    <string name="locality_hint">Please Enter Your Locality</string>
    <string name="city_hint">Please Select Your City</string>
    <string name="pincode_hint">Please Enter Your PinCode</string>
    <string name="mobile_hint">Please Enter Your Mobile Number</string>
    <string name="email_hint">Please Enter Your Email ID</string>
    <string name="services_hint">Please Select The Required Service</string>
    <string name="date_hint">Please Select the Date Of Function</string>
    <string name="delivery_mode_hint">Please Select the Mode Of Delivery</string>
    <string name="submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="reset">Reset Values</string>
    <string name="name_error">You did not enter the Name</string>
    <string name="address_error">You did not enter the Address</string>
    <string name="locality_error">You did not enter the Locality</string>
    <string name="city_error">You did not enter the City</string>
    <string name="pincode_error">You did not enter the PinCode</string>
    <string name="mobile_error">You did not enter the Mobile Number</string>
    <string name="email_error">You did not enter the Email ID</string>
    <string name="date_error">You did not enter the Function Date</string>
    <string name="end_date_error">You did not enter the Function End Date</string>
    <string name="price">Service Charge would be : </string>
    <string name="tax">Overall Tax would be : </string>
    <string name="discount">Overall Discount would be : </string>
    <string name="final_price">Overall Final Price would be : </string>
    <string name="mandatory_fields">The Fields which are marked with * are Mandatory Fields</string>
    <string name="alert_registration_submit_title">Hisanth Photography Price Details</string>
    <string name="alert_registration_submit_message">Please find the price details below</string>
    <string name="alert_registration_submit_positive_button">Submit with the Above Quote</string>
    <string name="alert_registration_module_name">registration</string>

    <string name="about_us1">Your Event will be Covered by a dedicated Photography and Videography team that understands the importance of a Wedding.</string>
    <string name="about_us2">Every event is treated as our own event and hence atmost care is given to every aspect of the event to make it very special and unique.</string>
    <string name="about_us3">We believe in referral clients and work to the utmost satisfaction of our client and their near and dear.</string>
    <string name="disclaimer1">Feel free to ask Customized package which match your budget from Customized Packages Tab. \n The final package price won\'t be negotiable. \n We believe that there is no discount in our hard work</string>
    <string name="disclaimer2">If you want demo videos, feel free to ask us and we will show you in our office. \n No Demo videos will be posted Online or in Application. \n We believe that customer privacy is very important</string>

    <string name="general_help1"><u><b>How to contact us ?</b></u> \n We can be contacted by Whatsapp, Facebook, Youtube, Google Maps, Email, SMS and Phone Call.  Please check the ways of contacting
        us in the "Contact Us" tab</string>
    <string name="general_help2"><u><b>Can I get any Discount in the services ?</b></u> \n The final package price won\'t be negotiable. \n We believe that there is no discount in our hard work</string>
    <string name="general_help3"><u><b>Can I customise My own Service packages ?</b></u> \n Feel free to ask Customized package which match your budget from Customized Packages Tab.</string>
    <string name="general_help4"><u><b>Is there a way to see demo videos / photos ?</b></u> \n If you want demo videos, feel free to ask us and we will show you in our office. \n No Demo videos will be posted Online or in Application. \n We believe that customer privacy is very important</string>
    <string name="general_help5"><u><b>Are you supporting with your services through Tamil Nadu ?</b></u> \n Currently we are supporting Madurai and Ramanathapuram only.  But we support
    all the cities of Tamil Nadu on Demand.</string>
    <string name="general_help6"><u><b>How much days will it take to get my photos / videos from the event date ?</b></u> \n We will delivery your contents within a week from your event date.</string>
    <string name="general_help7"><u><b>How can I collect my Photos / Videos ?</b></u> \n While registration, you can either select Self Collection or Door Delivery from Mode of Delivery
    Drop down.  The price will vary based on the selection.  You can also change the mode after submission also.  The charges may vary based on the change.</string>
    <string name="general_help8"><u><b>Do you offer Photo Albums and Video Albums ?</b></u> \n Yes we offer Photo / video Albums free of cost or with a Minimal charge based on
    the package selected by you.</string>
    <string name="general_help9"><u><b>Do you print Visiting Cards, Wedding cards and other gift cards ?</b></u> \n As of now we are not doing this service.  But in future, we have a plan to
    start this service also.</string>
    <string name="general_help10"><u><b>Do you print Flex banners and other banners ?</b></u> \n As of now we are not doing this service.  But in future, we have a plan to
    start this service also.</string>
    <string name="photo_help1"><u><b>What is Aerial Photography ?</b></u> \n As soon as our flight takes off, we love to shoot the landscape or city scene below which gives us an advantage of taking a picture from above.
          So, images that are captured from above is known as aerial photography.  Drones are used for this purpose.</string>
    <string name="photo_help2"><u><b>What is Architectural photography ?</b></u> \n Capturing an interesting form, shape or colour of the structure can be visually appealing.  Therefore visuals of
        buildings that are interesting fall under this genre.  We can include interiors or exteriors of buildings and even an interesting element of the design.</string>
    <string name="photo_help3"><u><b>What is Candid photography / Wedding Photography ?</b></u> \n This is a very popular genre of photography.  Moments captured spontaneously as they happen is known ascandid photography.
          The subjects are usually not aware of the photographer, so they appear very relaxed.  Wedding photography is a perfect example of this style of photography.</string>
    <string name="photo_help10"><u><b>What is Conceptual / fine art photography ?</b></u> \n Images that tell a story come under this genre.  In terms of conceptual / fine art photography, we can
        create our own fiction with characters in made-up environment. </string>
    <string name="photo_help4"><u><b>What is Documentary photography ?</b></u> \n Manual pictures that form a photo story come under this style.  It is about a particular subject or a story that a photographer wants to highlight.
          They are all objective pictures and can be about a war, social issues, science and so on.</string>
    <string name="photo_help5"><u><b>What is Fashion photography ?</b></u> \n Typically used to sell something, this type of photography lures customers by glamorising the product.
          They are generally very creative and visually very interesting and can be taken in any location like a studio, an apartment, a rundown building or anywhere outdoors.</string>
    <string name="photo_help6"><u><b>What is Food photography ?</b></u> \n Whether we are sharing an image of food served at a restaurant or on our dinner table, almost everyone seems to be at
        it today.  This type of photography is used by restaurants, websites or bloggers to entice customers to try and sell their products.</string>
    <string name="photo_help7"><u><b>What is Landscape photography ?</b></u> \n This is one of the most popular types of photography, as it can portray a scenery, or can even show an impact of
        environmental change.  We all love to capture a beautiful landscape when we see one. However, we need to wait for the right light to capture that perfect moment.</string>
    <string name="photo_help8"><u><b>What is Night-long exposure photography ?</b></u> \n it\'s a great way to capture how the world transforms after dark.  This type of photography requires
        good knowledge of how we use light, shutter speed and aperture.  These types of photos are interesting as the viewer gets to see some unusual aspects that cannot be
        seen by the naked eye. </string>
    <string name="photo_help9"><u><b>What is Photojournalism ?</b></u> \n This photography is similar to the documentary genre.  The only difference here is that a photographer captures live
        events as and when it happens and informs the world about it.  Examples of this style of photography is what we see every day in newspapers, magazines etc.</string>
    <string name="photo_help11"><u><b>What is Portraiture ?</b></u> \n Capturing people moods and expressions is an intriguing subject for photographers.  They can be close-up images,
        body portraits etc.  Typically the face is the focus of this type of photography.</string>
    <string name="photo_help12"><u><b>What is Sport photography ?</b></u> \n This category involves getting up-close to the action in a very fast-paced and action-packed setting.  Sports events
        are captured with very long lenses as we usually see photographers during an event.</string>
    <string name="photo_help13"><u><b>What is Street photography ?</b></u> \n Capturing ordinary, everyday life in public spaces or life as it happens is known as street photography.
        It is very similar to candid photography, but the photographer documents the public space as he or she sees it.</string>
    <string name="photo_help14"><u><b>What is War photography ?</b></u> \n Capturing images of conflicts in war-torn areas fall under this genre.
        War photographers usually put their life in danger to cover the event.  War photography can even document the aftermath of war.</string>
    <string name="photo_help15"><u><b>What is Wildlife photography ?</b></u> \n This is a very challenging type of photography, as it might be difficult to capture animals in their proper habitat.
        This style requires proper technical skills and it needs to be planned accordingly.  In wildlife photography, you need to be absolutely comfortable with your camera\'s settings.
        If you are not quick enough, you might miss the perfect shot.</string>
    <string name="video_help1"><u><b>What is Broadcast Commercial Videography ?</b></u> \n Although this type of video is perhaps the most expensive on the list, it can also generate
        the most return on investment if shown enough times on popular television channels.  You should only attempt a television commercial, however, when you have the budget to do a
        high quality production and can afford to do a lot of television advertising, since repetition on a popular channel is the key to success.</string>
    <string name="video_help2"><u><b>What is Company Profile Videography ?</b></u> \n One of the best ways to introduce your company to consumers is through a company profile video.
        It can include messages from the CEO, other top officials and product experts. This type of video helps reach a common ground with people within and beyond your target market.
        By showing pictures of inside the enterprise and giving a little company history, along with its mission statement and unique marketing proposition, viewers can get a clear idea
        of the company\'s purpose in the market.</string>
    <string name="video_help3"><u><b>What is Conferences and Seminars Videography ?</b></u> \n Similar to event videos, conference or seminar videos allow consumers to watch your
        company presentations without leaving home.  The beauty of these type of videos, like most videos not necessarily designed for television broadcast, is that there are no time
        constraints. You are free to offer content depth that cannot be found elsewhere.</string>
    <string name="video_help4"><u><b>What is Customer Testimonial Videography ?</b></u> \n One of the best ways to connect with consumers is to offer product reviews by actual customers
        who have tested the product.  It\'s becoming an important part of marketing since online shoppers want quick answers as to whether a product is worth buying and lives up to
        promotional claims.</string>
    <string name="video_help5"><u><b>What is Drone Videography ?</b></u> \n Videos taken by Drones for the Aerial view effects mainly used in Weddings and Travel activities.  It gives
    a different look and feel for the customers from the Aerial view.</string>
    <string name="video_help6"><u><b>What is Event Documentation Videography ?</b></u> \n It\'s advantageous for your company to roll video on events that you present to the public or
        that document your milestones.  These videos become achievement evidence that you can showcase on your website and share through social media. It\'s a compelling visual way to
        develop an archive of company history.</string>
    <string name="video_help7"><u><b>What is Industrial Videography ?</b></u> \n Aimed at audiences within a specific industry, an industrial video is designed to be informative
        about products, services and industry trends. It can be used for fundraising to get more investors involved and it can be used for business to business marketing,
        particularly at trade shows.</string>
    <string name="video_help8"><u><b>What is Internal Communication Videography ?</b></u> \n Known as an "address to camera," an internal video can be directed at staff, vendors or
        clients.  It is an effective way to explain a company policy or other internal information.</string>
    <string name="video_help9"><u><b>What is Music Videography ?</b></u> \n Traditionally most of the Music Albums are shooted inside a music studio for a  more professional look which
    is then posted in social media or developed into DVDs / CDs.</string>
    <string name="video_help10"><u><b>What is Online Commercial Videography ?</b></u> \n An online commercial differs from a television commercial in the sense that it is not restricted
        by a 30 or 60 second time limit and it doesn\'t require as large of a budget.  Many online commercials are low budget and simply rely on good storytelling, which can be an
        important key to going viral on YouTube.  Small and medium businesses are finding this concept to be very useful.</string>
    <string name="video_help11"><u><b>What is Promotional Videography ?</b></u> \n Similar to online commercials, promotional videos are designed to showcase products and services except
        they are not necessarily made just for online consumption.  They can also be distributed through DVDs and packaged with other media as well as shared on social media.</string>
    <string name="video_help12"><u><b>What is Real Estate Videography ?</b></u> \n Nowadays Real Estate Shootings are trendy across India and all the promotors uses Videos as demos and
    advertisements for their properties.  Your business becomes success due to the advertisement effects.</string>
    <string name="video_help13"><u><b>What is Staff Training Videography ?</b></u> \n You can accelerate your staff learning curve by using demonstration and training videos.
        The power of the visual medium allows team members to watch the video over and over again until the information is understood.
        It\'s an excellent way to clarify "how to" steps. Quality training videos that use clear communication can cut down on training expenses since they eliminate the need for
        repetitious instruction to accommodate new team members.</string>
    <string name="video_help14"><u><b>What is Talent Recruitment Videography ?</b></u> \n Designed to promote your company as a good employer to attract skilled workers, recruitment videos
        can help HR departments target specific markets for recruiting the most appropriate talent.  They can used in conjunction with classified ads on employment websites.</string>
    <string name="video_help15"><u><b>What is Wedding Videography ?</b></u> \n Traditional way of capturing the Weddings.  This art is living with us for the past 100 years and it has
    become a custom now along with other rituals.</string>

    <string name="corporate_packages">Corporate Packages</string>
    <string name="personal_packages">Personal Packages</string>
    <string name="customized_packages">Customized Packages</string>

    <string name="contact_us">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="mail_id">Our Mail ID : (Click to Send Mail To Us) \n hisanthphotography@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="facebook">Contact Us in Facebook (Click to Open our Facebook Page) \n hisanthphotography@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="whatsapp">Whatsapp Us in : (Click to Whatsapp Us) \n +919790495863</string>
    <string name="youtube">Check Our Youtube Channel (Click to Open) \n hisanthphotography@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="mobile_number1">Our Mobile Number 1 : (Click To Call) \n +919790495863</string>
    <string name="mobile_number2">Our Mobile Number 2 : (Click To Call) \n +918148148281</string>
    <string name="map_label">Locate us in Google Maps : </string>
    <string name="map_address">Locate us in Google Maps : (Loaded Below)</string>
    <string name="static_mobile_number1">+919790495863</string>
    <string name="static_mobile_number2">+918148148281</string>
    <string name="static_email_id">hisanthphotography@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="static_facebook">+919790495863</string>
    <string name="static_whatsapp">919790495863</string>
    <string name="static_youtube">UC_5R469ekdDvHUpiRsc_tEw</string>
    <string name="static_tel">tel:</string>
    <string name="static_mail_subject">Hisanth Photography Contact Us Query</string>
    <string name="static_mail_select_title">Send email using...</string>
    <string name="static_mail_error">No email clients installed.</string>
    <string name="static_sms">sms:</string>
    <string name="simple_date_format">dd/MM/yyyy</string>
    <string name="map_title">Hisanth Photography Office</string>
    <string name="map_snippet">You can see us there</string>

    <string name="alert_location_title">Enable Location</string>
    <string name="alert_location_message">Your Locations Settings is set to \'Off\'. \n Please Enable Location to use this app</string>
    <string name="alert_location_positive_button">Location Settings</string>
    <string name="alert_location_module_name">location</string>
    <string name="alert_generic_positive_button">Location Settings</string>
    <string name="alert_permission_message">1. To send SMS to the Owner after you successfully submit your request, SMS Permission is required. \n2. To Call the Owner as soon as you click the mobile number, Call permission is required. \n3. To Automatically Capture your address instead of you typing, Location permission is required.</string>
    <string name="go_to_settings">Go to settings and enable permissions</string>

    <string-array name="city_array">
        <item>Please Select Your City *</item>
        <item>Ariyalur</item>
        <item>Chennai</item>
        <item>Coimbatore</item>
        <item>Cuddalore</item>
        <item>Dharmapuri</item>
        <item>Dindigul</item>
        <item>Erode</item>
        <item>Kanchipuram</item>
        <item>Kanyakumari</item>
        <item>Karur</item>
        <item>Krishnagiri</item>
        <item>Madurai</item>
        <item>Nagapattinam</item>
        <item>Namakkal</item>
        <item>Perambalur</item>
        <item>Pudukkottai</item>
        <item>Ramanathapuram</item>
        <item>Salem</item>
        <item>Sivagangai</item>
        <item>Thanjavur</item>
        <item>The Nilgiris</item>
        <item>Theni</item>
        <item>Thoothukudi</item>
        <item>Tiruchirappalli</item>
        <item>Tirunelveli</item>
        <item>Tiruppur</item>
        <item>Tiruvallur</item>
        <item>Tiruvannamalai</item>
        <item>Tiruvarur</item>
        <item>Vellore</item>
        <item>Viluppuram</item>
        <item>Virudhunagar</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="service_array">
        <item>Please Select The Required Service *</item>
        <item>Aerial Photography</item>
        <item>Architectural Photography</item>
        <item>Candid Photography / Wedding Photography</item>
        <item>Conceptual/ fine art Photography</item>
        <item>Documentary Photography</item>
        <item>Fashion Photography</item>
        <item>Food Photography</item>
        <item>Landscape Photography</item>
        <item>Night-long exposure Photography</item>
        <item>Photojournalism</item>
        <item>Portraiture</item>
        <item>Sport Photography</item>
        <item>Street Photography</item>
        <item>War Photography</item>
        <item>Wildlife Photography</item>
        <item>Broadcast Commercial Videography</item>
        <item>Company Profile Videography</item>
        <item>Conferences and Seminars Videography</item>
        <item>Customer Testimonial Videography</item>
        <item>Drone Videography</item>
        <item>Event Documentation Videography</item>
        <item>Industrial Videography</item>
        <item>Internal Communication Videography</item>
        <item>Music Videography</item>
        <item>Online Commercial Videography</item>
        <item>Promotional Videography</item>
        <item>Real Estate Videography</item>
        <item>Staff Training Videography</item>
        <item>Talent Recruitment Videography</item>
        <item>Wedding Videography</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="function_array">
        <item>Please Select The Required Function *</item>
        <item>Wedding</item>
        <item>Pre Wedding Shoot</item>
        <item>Engagement</item>
        <item>Birthday</item>
        <item>Others</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="budget_array">
        <item>Less Than Rs. 30,000</item>
        <item>Rs. 30,000 - Rs. 50,000</item>
        <item>Rs. 50,000 - Rs. 75,000</item>
        <item>Rs. 75,000 - Rs. 1 lakh</item>
        <item>Above Rs. 1 Lakh</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="mode_of_delivery_array">
        <item>Please Select the Mode Of Delivery *</item>
        <item>Self Collection</item>
        <item>Door Delivery</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
